(Leonard:)Really?
(Raj:)I know.
(Sheldon:)It's not fair.
(Sheldon:)Let the anger
go, buddy.
(Sheldon:)You just...
(Sheldon:)you relax all
your muscles.
(Sheldon:)Except for your pubococcygeus
and anal sphincter.
(Sheldon:)Let's keep those tight.
Uh, that-that's not necessary.
(Sheldon:)It is-- they're what hold back
the urine and the feces.
Look, maybe-maybe
you shouldn't read it.
(Sheldon:)It'll only make you feel worse.
"Cooper and his team"?
(Sheldon:)You should know
I had nothing to do with that.
(Sheldon:)Uh...
(Leonard:)at least they're talking
about the theory.
(Leonard:)I mean, that's what's important.
(Sheldon:)You know, you're right.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. You know, it's like
when Stan Lee and Steve Ditko
(Sheldon:)created Spider-Man.
(Sheldon:)Stan Lee may get all the credit,
(Sheldon:)but Steve Ditko knows
he was just as important.
(Sheldon:)Even though Stan Lee gets
to be in all the Marvel movies.
And-and he's far richer.
(Sheldon:)And he's a household name,
you know?